We shake it...
We take it..
with pride
and show!
We like it...
exciting
and ready
to go!
I'm projecting and reflecting desire
for you to come into my life.
The rays of this day will outshine them all
for me and you to get along.
It's like running away with the wind in our face, it's like flying
(flying!)
and you and I are open wide.
It's like running away with the wind in our face, it's like flying
(flying!)
and you and I are open wide.
I feel so excited and delighted today
'cause you decided to be in my life.
It's like running away with the wind in our face, it's like flying
(flying!)
and you and I are open wide.
The show...
the electric show!
I get around the world upon your freeways
it's true when you let it go.