I'm a dreamer... hidden power...
My world... made of dreams, love and uncertainty
but there are things lying hidden that I cannot imagine.
Just like the trees, I face the sky, gazing straight at you.
I want to find my dream... I want to make it come true.
There is nothing I can't overcome if only I believe.
Just like singing... just like miracles
feelings can change everything.
I'm sure, so sure... it's surprising.
I'm a dreamer... hidden power...
A world yet unseen...
no matter what awaits me there
even if it's not perfect, I won't be afraid.
Birds travel on the wind,
on a journey from today to tomorrow.
I want to tell you... I want to shout it.
I am only one person in this world
but like a prayer, like a star, the smallest lights
want to become stronger someday.
There are limitless possibilities... right here in my grasp.
It's gonna be your world.
Just like singing, just like miracles
feelings can change everything.
I'm sure, so sure... it's surprising.